(Sheldon:)But I'm sure those Cool Ranch
Doritos are doing the trick.
(Scene:)Sheldon.
(gasps)
Leonard!
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm so happy
to see you.
(Leonard:)Are you okay?
Oh, I'm fine.
(Sheldon:)Why did you come?
(Amy:)What do you mean,
why did I come?
(Amy:)You're my boyfriend.
(Amy:)I haven't seen you
in over a month.
(Amy:)I just drove six hours
to help you out.
(Amy:)Don't you have
anything to say besides,
"Why did you come?"
(Sheldon:)I do, but...
(Sheldon:)I feel uncomfortable
saying it out loud
(Sheldon:)in front of these
police officers.
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Amy:)Whisper it.
(Sheldon(whispers):)Shotgun.
(Leonard:)So, Sheldon, tell
us about your trip.
(Leonard:)Where'd you go?
(Sheldon:)Where didn't I go?
(Sheldon:)I went to New York,
(Sheldon:)Chicago, Atlanta, Denver,